{
  "topic": "English Grammar Quiz",
  "version": "0.0.1",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 10000,
      "question": "My kids ___ already gone to bed when I got home.",
      "options": ["had", "has", "have", "did"],
      "answer": "had"
    },
    {
      "id": 10001,
      "question": "Can you think __ the missing word in this sentence?",
      "answer": "of"
    },
    {
      "id": 10002,
      "question": "I looked everywhere, but I _____ not find my keys.",
      "answer": "could"
    },
    {
      "id": 10003,
      "question": "Sheâ€™s getting home the day _____ tomorrow.",
      "options": ["before", "after", "later", "previous"],
      "answer": "after"
    },
    {
      "id": 10004,
      "question": "Gandhiji ___ a great leader",
      "answer": "was"
    },
    {
      "id": 10005,
      "question": "Ramesh took ___ book from me.",
      "options": ["their", "my","all" ,"his"],
      "answer": "his"
    },
    {
      "id": 10006,
      "question": "He ____ to the market yesterday. (go)",
      "answer": "went"
    },
    {
      "id": 10007,
      "question": "The sun _____ in the morning. (rise)",
      "answer": "rises"
    },
    {
      "id": 10008,
      "question": "Be pure __ heart.",
      "answer": "in"
    },
    {
      "id": 10009,
      "question": "Do not speak ill __ others.",
      "answer": "of"
    },
    {
      "id": 10010,
      "question": "Babar laid ____ his life for his son.",
      "answer": "down"
    },
    {
      "id": 10011,
      "question": "Sohan was __ honest boy.",
      "answer": "an"
    },
    {
      "id": 10012,
      "question": "I __ going to the market.",
      "answer": "am"
    },
    {
      "id": 10013,
      "question": "They ___ leaving today.",
      "options": ["is", "did", "a", "are"],
      "answer": "are"
    },
    {
      "id": 10014,
      "question": "Sita was married __ Ram.",
      "answer": "to"
    },
    {
      "id": 10015,
      "question": "The japanese ___ a very hard working people.",
      "answer": "are"
    }
  ]
}
